{
    "questions": [
        {
            "queno": "1",
            "question": "Q1. How hot is the surface of the sun?",
            "options": [
                "1,233 K",
                "5,778 K",
                "12,130 K",
                "101,300 K"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "5,778 K"
        },
        {
            "queno": "2",
            "question": "Q2. What is the scientific name of a butterfly?",
            "options": [
                "Apis",
                "Coleoptera",
                "Formicidae",
                "Rhopalocera"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Rhopalocera"
        },
        {
            "queno": "3",
            "question": "Q3. Who are the actors in The Internship?",
            "options": [
                "Ben Stiller, Jonah Hill",
                "Courteney Cox, Matt LeBlanc",
                "Kaley Cuoco, Jim Parsons",
                "Vince Vaughn, Owen Wilson"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Vince Vaughn, Owen Wilson"
        },
        {
            "queno": "4",
            "question": "Q4. What is the capital of Spain?",
            "options": [
                "Berlin",
                "Buenos Aires",
                "Madrid",
                "San Juan"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Madrid"
        },
        {
            "queno": "5",
            "question": "Q5. What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
            "options": [
                "Black, Red",
                "Blue, Orange",
                "White, Burnt Orange",
                "White, Old gold, Gold"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "White, Burnt Orange"
        },
        {
            "queno": "6",
            "question": "Q6. What is 70 degrees Fahrenheit in Celsius?",
            "options": [
                "18.8889",
                "20",
                "21.1111",
                "158"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "21.1111"
        },
        {
            "queno": "7",
            "question": "Q7. When was Mahatma Gandhi born?",
            "options": [
                "October 2, 1869",
                "December 15, 1872",
                "July 18, 1918",
                "January 15, 1929"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "October 2, 1869"
        },
        {
            "queno": "8",
            "question": "Q8. How far is the moon from Earth?",
            "options": [
                "7,918 miles (12,742 km)",
                "86,881 miles (139,822 km)",
                "238,400 miles (384,400 km)",
                "35,980,000 miles (57,910,000 km)"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "238,400 miles (384,400 km)"
        },
        {
            "queno": "9",
            "question": "Q9. What is 65 times 52?",
            "options": [
                "117",
                "3120",
                "3380",
                "3520"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "3380"
        },
        {
            "queno": "10",
            "question": "Q10. How tall is Mount Everest?",
            "options": [
                "6,683 ft (2,037 m)",
                "7,918 ft (2,413 m)",
                "19,341 ft (5,895 m)",
                "29,029 ft (8,847 m)"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "29,029 ft (8,847 m)"
        },
        {
            "queno": "11",
            "question": "Q11. When did The Avengers come out?",
            "options": [
                "May 2, 2008",
                "May 4, 2012",
                "May 3, 2013",
                "April 4, 2014"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "May 4, 2012"
        },
        {
            "queno": "12",
            "question": "Q12. What is 48,879 in hexidecimal?",
            "options": [
                "0x18C1",
                "0xBEEF",
                "0xDEAD",
                "0x12D591"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "0xBEEF"
        },
        {
            "queno": "13",
            "question": "Q13. To which object does the location property belong?",
            "options": [
                "Window",
                "Position",
                "Element",
                "Location"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Window"
        },
        {
            "queno": "14",
            "question": "Q14. Which of the following is not a framework?",
            "options": [
                "jQuery",
                ".NET",
                "Javascript",
                "None of the mentioned"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Javascript"
        },
        {
            "queno": "15",
            "question": "Q15. How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?",
            "options": [
                "alert('Hello World');",
                "msgBox('Hello World');",
                "prompt('Hello World');",
                "alertBox('Hello World');"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "alert('Hello World');"
        },
        {
            "queno": "16",
            "question": "Q16. How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
            "options": [
                "function = myFunction()",
                "function:myFunction()",
                "function myFunction()",
                "None of the mentioned"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "function myFunction()"
        },
        {
            "queno": "17",
            "question": "Q17. How do you call a function named 'myFunction'?",
            "options": [
                "myFunction()",
                "call function myFunction()",
                "call myFunction()",
                "None of the mentioned"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "myFunction()"
        },
        {
            "queno": "18",
            "question": "Q18. What are variables used for in JavaScript Programs?",
            "options": [
                "Storing numbers, dates, or other values",
                "Varying randomly",
                "Causing high-school algebra flashbacks",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Storing numbers, dates, or other values"
        },
        {
            "queno": "19",
            "question": "Q19. Which of the following can't be done with client-side JavaScript?",
            "options": [
                "Validating a form",
                " Sending a form's contents by email",
                "Storing the form's contents to a database file on the server",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Storing the form's contents to a database file on the server"
        },
        {
            "queno": "20",
            "question": "Q20. Which of the following is not considered a JavaScript operator?",
            "options": [
                "new",
                "this",
                "delete",
                "typeof"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "this"
        }
    ]
}